Jordan Rudge

sadravioli.github.io/cv/ github.com/SadRavioli
London, United Kingdom linkedin.com/in/jordan-rudge
jrudge56@gmail.com

Summary

Full-stack web developer with over three years of experience in designing, developing, and maintaining responsive web solutions. Skilled in C#, .NET, HTML/CSS, DevExpress, JavaScript, and advanced SQL techniques. I have now led multiple projects adding new features to industry leading site, and have in doing some led planning and requirement gathering.

Experience

Fullstack Web Developer The ECPR Apr 2022 - Present

- Project lead of the ECPR's new **prizes system**, that can handle many different prize formats and conditions. Additionally, this has provided an improved system for a colleague to work in, saving them a lot of time.
- Led the creation of the **shop area** of the ECPR website. A user can navigate a paged product grid by series, subject, date published or search string. This provided a new revenue stream for the company.
- Implemented Tawk. To chatbot/knowledgebase to the site while removing TalkJS, saving the company multiple thousands of pounds a year.
- Enhanced and maintained the ECPR website(s) using C#, .NET/Entity Framework, and SQL.
- Developed responsive front-end interfaces with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and DevExpress.
- Configured database updates and structures through the codebase to support new features and pages.
- Collaborated with different teams to implement new features and improve user experience.
- Spearheaded the refactoring of legacy systems to modern technologies, improving reliability and maintainability.

Frontend Developer Nottingham County Fair Dec 2019 - Feb 2020

• Developed the map and parking location features for the Nottingham County Fair appusing Swift.

Education

BSc (Hons) in Computer Science with Games Sep 2018 - August 2021 Nottingham Trent University Nottingham, United Kingdom

Skills

Backend Development: C#, .NET Framework, Entity Framework, SQL, Python

Frontend Development: HTML5 / CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, DevExpress

Database Technologies: SQL Server

Development Tools: Visual Studio, SSMS, Azure Devops/Git, DevTools

Testing & QA: Unit testing, performance optimisation, accessibility evaluation tools

(WAVE)

Languages: English

Certifications

Advanced SQL Feb 2024
Acuity Training London, United Kingdom
Azure Al Fundamentals August 2021
Microsoft Nottingham, United Kingdom